# **HUBERT BARAN**

Web & Al developer

## CONTACT

- +48137878707
- **■** Hubert0129Baran@hotmail.com
- @TalentedDeveloper

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Lodz**

October 2015~ Feburary 2019

Mathematics & Computer Science

### SKILLS

- Programming languages
   Python, JavaScript, PHP, C#
- Web development skills

HTML, CSS/SASS,
JavaScript/TypeScript
React(Hooks,Redux), Next.js
Vue.js, Nuxt.js
PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter
Node.js, Express.js
Django
Tailwind CSS
WordPress, WooCommerce
SQlite,MySQL, MongoDB,
PostgreSQL

- Al development skills
   TensorFlow, Keras,
   openCV, Pytorch, PyQt5
- Softwares and Tools
   GitVS Code Linux GitHub
   VisualStudio, Postman,
   Pycharm, RESTful API

#### **PROFILE**

I am Hubert Baran. I am a talented Web & Al developer with 5 years of experience in development, expertise technologies, can-do attitude, high goals and strong educational background in programing. I am also Result-driven, self-motivated, dedicated and potential developer with high attention to detail. I am productive in both teambased and self-managed projects.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## During the university

October 2015 - February 2019

- Own Software development skills, Modern mathematics
- Many Web and AI example projects
- Memorable project is for University website administrator site maintenance (Responsible for backend) https://www.uni.lodz.pl/

## Internship in Versio software company

February 2019 - August 2019

- Company's website maintenance and management http://versio.pl/
- Company's website redesign and development with React but it was awarded to the other because I became an employee

# Working as an employee in Versio software company

August 2019 - December 2021

- Memorable projects are: https://anatechnology.net/, https://havenly.com/
- Memorable Al project development( Image Recognition system, and chatbot for the company's business)

### Working as a freelancer

December 2021 - Current time

- Memorable projects are: https://stickdatei-vektordatei.de/, https://arabfor.sa/#/
- Al projects are: Image recognition for the APP https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.arabfor.arabforClient